翻譯: 149 抱個熊
校對: super死打斯基
後期: holi
我  本  堅  強
第一季        第一集
電波誠譯
壓製: 凱撒
聖誕快樂 姐妹們
Merry Christmas, sisters.
太美了 Kimmy修女
Just beautiful, Sister Kimmy.
你們誰是我的
Now, which one of you guys have been chosen
神秘聖誕老人呀
as my Secret Santa?
不可說 Kimmy修女
We can't not tell, Sister Kimmy.
說了就不是秘密了 這都不懂嗎
Then 't wouldn't be a secret. Duh.
*末日到來 末日到來*
*Apocalypse, apocalypse*
*我們的愚蠢使末日到來*
*We caused it with our dumbness*
哦不 噴火怪
Oh, no. Oh, no! Fire monsters!
上 上
Let's go! Let's go!
- 走 走 走  - 找到她們了
- Move, move, move! - We found them!
Kimmy 我覺得我們數錯日子了
Kimmy, I think we counted wrong.
- 現在不是聖誕  - 但是一切都在
- It's not Christmas. - But it's here.
世界還在
It's all still here.
今天在印第安納州登斯維爾出現了一個奇跡
A miracle today in Durnsville, Indiana.
四個女人從地底下的一個末日邪教中被救出
Four women rescued from an underground apocalypse cult
特大 新聞
找到白人女性
還有一位西班牙裔女性
據說是被一名
allegedly run by self...
自稱"Richard Wayne Gary Wayne牧師救世主"的人所掌控
Proclaimed messiah Reverend Richard Wayne Gary Wayne,
特大新聞
邪教領袖因舉止怪異
在沃爾瑪被逮捕
此人最為人熟知的身份是在Yelp上
best known to Yelp users in this area...
被評為登斯維爾最差的婚禮DJ
As Durnsville's worst wedding DJ.
特大新聞
邪教領袖Richard Wayne Gary Wayne
化名methuzalophsteron已被逮捕
現在在我身邊的是
I am now joined by a neighbor
目睹了整個過程的鄰居
who watched all the drama unfold,
Walter Bankston  Bankston先生
Walter Bankston. Mr. Bankston?
哦 事情是這樣的
Oh, yeah, what had happened was...
特大新聞
家住邪教基地附近
*當時我正在外面*
*I was outside*
*幫我孫子拆輪胎*
*Cutting up bike tires for my grandson*
*闖出四千輛警車*
*When out of nowhere 40-hundred police vehicles*
本地婦女從末日邪教中被救出
特大新聞
*氣勢洶洶喲*
*Came bookin'*
*他們立馬炸開那*
*They ran bustin' up*
特大新聞
消息稱:邪教成員數年在地底生活
被告知世界已滅亡
*奇怪白老頭的房子*
*In that weird old white dude's house*
*他在那兒有個邪教呢*
*He had a cult up in there*
*白人總乾些詭異的案子*
*White dudes hold the record for creepy crimes*
*但是女人們可真牛逼啊*
*But females are strong as hell*
*簡直堅不可摧 她們活下來了 臥槽*
*Unbreakable they alive, damn it*
*真是個奇跡 堅不可摧*
*It's a miracle. Unbreakable*
*她們活下來了 臥槽*
*They alive, damn it*
*但是女人們可真牛逼啊*
*But females are strong as hell*
這就是那段瘋傳的視頻
They are the subjects of that viral video.
鼴鼠女混接視頻瘋傳
現在在我身邊的是印第安納鼴鼠女
And joining me now for their first exclusive interview,
這是她們第一份獨家專訪 女士們 歡迎
the Indiana Mole Women. Ladies, welcome.
- 謝謝  - 謝謝 Bryant
- Thank you. - Thank you, Bryant.
多年來 你們一直被
For years, you were told
印第安納鼴鼠女訪談
15年苦難終於結束
Richard Wayne Gary Wayne牧師告知
by Reverend Richard Wayne Gary Wayne
世界已經毀滅
that the world had ended.
是的 Richard牧師告訴我們
Yes, Reverend Richard told us
在八年級時被綁架
那是一場核彈末日
that there had been a nuclear apocalypse
地球已被烤焦
and that the Earth was scorched
處處是火海
and there were lakes of fire and stuff.
Cyndee 你是第一位
Cyndee, you were the first young woman
被迫加入這個邪教的女人
forced into this cult.
是的 我在一家約克牛排店
Yes, I had waited on Reverend Richard
第一個被帶進Wayne的"教堂"裡
做服務員
a bunch of times
接待過Richard牧師好多次
at a York Steak House I worked at,
有一天晚上他邀請我到他的車上
and one night he invited me out to his car
看些小兔子
to see some baby rabbits.
我不想顯得不禮貌 於是
And I didn't want to be rude, so...
就這樣了
here we are.
女人為了避免顯得不禮貌
I'm always amazed at what women will do
真是什麼都會乾
because they're afraid of being rude.
- 是啊  - Gretchen
- Yeah. - Gretchen.
你是自願加入這個邪教的
You joined this cult willingly.
是 他在克雷格廣告網上買了一些我的頭髮
Yes, the Reverend had bought some of my hair on Craigslist,
於是我們就開始互通郵件
and we started emailing,
邪教成員
然後我就覺得他說的真的有道理
and I just thought he had some real good ideas.
哇 Donna Maria 你是為一家
Wow. Donna Maria, you were working
叫"幸福女傭"的公司工作是吧
for a company called Happy Maids?
被綁架的"幸福女傭"
你被騙進牧師的房子
You were lured into the reverend's house.
你以為是去幹活的
You thought this was a job.
對 幸福女傭
Sí, Happy Maids.
跟這些女人們住了15年
15 years living with these other women,
你還是沒學會英語
and yet you still never learned to speak English.
這幫賤人也沒學西班牙語 所以
女士們 你們被給予了
Ladies, you've been given
一個重生的絕好機會
an amazing second chance at life.
人們給鼴鼠女基金會捐獻了
People have donated thousands of dollars
成千上萬塊錢
to the Mole Women fund.
我們感激不盡
And we are so grateful.
但是說實話 我們不是很喜歡那稱呼
But, honestly, we don't love that name.
鼴鼠女 接下來呢
So, Mole Women, what happens next?
你們準備幹什麼
What do you do now?
應該就是回到登斯維爾
Probably just go back to Durnsville,
把我牙套取下來
get my braces off.
回印第安納 當幸福女傭
Indiana. Happy Maids.
我現在得跟你走對吧 我算是嫁給你了
I go with you now, yes? I'm married to you?
- 不不不  - 不 Gretchen 不
- No, no, no, no. - No, Gretchen, no.
Kimmy 你呢
Kimmy, what about you?
Kimmy
Kimmy?
好的 廣告回來介紹秋季沙拉的錯誤做法
Okay, when we come back, fall salad mistakes.
還有 一位鼴鼠女將得到一個造型大轉變的驚喜
Plus one of the Mole Women gets an ambush makeover.
謝謝你們 受害者們 謝謝
Thank you, victims. Thank you.
祝你們好運 謝謝 受害者們
Good luck. Thank you, victims.
謝謝 受害者們
Thank you, victims.
停 拜託靠邊停一下
Stop! Pull over, please.
Kimmy 你在幹什麼
Kimmy, what are you doing?
- 我不回去  - 什麼
- I'm not going back. - What?
- 我要留在這裡  - Kimmy 這太離譜了
- I'm staying here. - Kimmy, that's crazy.
你只有初中文憑
You have a middle school education!
你在這裡活不下去的
You won't make it here!
就像Richard牧師總說的
It's like Reverend Richard always says.
- 我們就是垃圾 Kimmy  - 不對
- We're just garbage, Kimmy. - That's not true!
我們不是垃圾 我們是活生生的人
We're not garbage. We're human beings.
我必須過上正常的生活
I have to get my life back.
所有登斯維爾的人
Everybody in Durnsville
一輩子都會把我看做是一個受害者
is always gonna look at me like I'm a victim,
但我並不只是個受害者
and that's not what I am.
如果你是認真的話
Well, if you're really gonna do this...
拿些我的鼴鼠基金走
Take some of my Mole Fund money.
現在一個汽水就要5刀呢
I mean, a pop here is, like, $5.
還有 我是你的神秘聖誕老人
Also, I'm your Secret Santa.
再見
Adiós.
我們在室外跑步耶
We're running! Outside!
我要轉一整圈
I'm gonna go all the way around!
我的天啊 她真做到了
Oh, my God, she did it!
我要吃糖當晚餐
I'm having candy for dinner.
你應該自由
You deserve to be free.
公寓 唔
Apartments, hmm.
嘿 我看見你偷這個了
Hey. I saw you steal this.
你家長呢 就你一個人嗎
Where is your grown-up? Are you alone?
或者您是什麼很小隻的商人嗎 先生
Or are you some kind of tiny businessman, sir?
- 危險陌生人  - 我不是什麼危險陌生人
- Stranger danger! - I'm not stranger danger!
我可是專逮危險陌生人的
I'm a stranger danger ranger!
對不起打擾一下 女士
Uh, excuse me. Ma'am?
要貨的嗎 海沃因
You want smoke? Her-ron?
- 我來這是為了那個廣告  - 招室友廣告
- Uh, I'm here about the ad? - The roommate ad.
天啊 你是為了那個廣告來的
My God, you're here about the ad.
這棟樓是我的 來
I own the building. Come on.
這是個地下有窗公寓
It's a garden-level maisonette.
哎呀 你看起來真不錯
Look at you! You look so nice.
Titus是個特別特別好的男孩
And Titus is a very, very sweet boy.
外表強硬
A little crusty on the outside
內心柔軟 像個法式麵包
but a soft heart, like a wonderful French roll.
- 黑的  - 他媽的誰啊
- But black. - Who the fuck is it?
- 親愛的 是Lillian  - 哦
- It's Lillian, dear. - Oh.
他能有個室友
It's gonna be wonderful
太好了
for him to have a roommate,
因為他非常孤獨但才華橫溢
because he's very isolated but so talented
鬱郁不得志的天才
but disillusioned but a genius.
還有他單身但非常基
And he's single but very gay.
還有他不知道我發了那廣告
And he doesn't know I placed the ad.
怎麼了 Lillian 這是誰
What is it, Lillian? Who is this?
我是你的新室友
I'm your new roommate.
- 你能把我怎麼著  - Lillian 我可是個模範租客
- Okay, so sue me. - Lillian, I'm a model tenant!
- 你需要個室友  - 我一點也不吵
- You need a roommate. - I don't make noise.
我也不炸魚
I don't fry fish.
親愛的 你也不交房租
Honey, you also don't pay the rent.
因為我沒錢
Because I don't have money.
你知道我不想把你趕走
You know I do not want to evict you.
考慮一下她 好嗎
Just consider her, please?
你的現在住址是哪裡
What is your current address?
下一個問題
Next question.
我能看一下你最近的工作證明
May I see a recent letter of employment
- 或者兩份最近的工資單嗎  - 不能 不能
- or two recent pay stumps? - No and no.
- 你在哪裡工作  - 還沒有工作
- Where do you work? - Nowhere yet.
我說你別逗我了
I pronounce you ridiculous.
你有了哥屋恩作再來
Come back when you got a J-O-B!
他說的沒錯 我確實需要個工作
He's right. I am gonna need a job.
親愛的 你找到工作再回來
Honey, you come back here with a job,
- 這地方就讓你住了  - 謝謝
- the place is yours. - Thanks.
哦對了
Yeah. Oh!
別穿那黃色毛衣
But don't wear that yellow sweater,
跛子幫會覺得你是香蕉男孩一夥的
'cause the Crips'll think you're in the Banana Boys.
跛子幫 美國的黑幫團體 代表色為藍色 他們的死對頭浴血幫的代表色為紅色
那是個新的黑幫
It's a new gang.
沒剩什麼好顏色了
There weren't any good colors left.
很高興認識你
Nice to meet ya!
嗨 我叫Kimmy
Hi, I'm Kimmy.
我熱愛你們的產品
I'm a big fan of your products,
特別是鯊魚軟糖
particularly the shark gummies,
我只在你們這兒見過這種糖
which I hadn't seen elsewhere.
我想問問你們有沒有什麼
And I'm interested in any employment opportunities
招人的職位
that you might have...
- 你住哪兒  - 危險陌生人
- Where do you live? - Stranger danger!
謝天謝地 你是狗狗按摩師嗎
Thank God. Are you the dog masseuse?
不 女士 我找到你的兒子了
No. Ma'am, I found your son.
Buckley Hunong在哪兒
Buckley? Where's Hunong?
她從不來接我 所以我就自己走回家而已
She never picked me up, so I was just walking home.
騙人
Liar!
不好意思 你是學校職員嗎
I'm sorry. And you work for the school?
- 不  - 所以你是優步司機
- No. - So you're an Uber driver.
- 不  - 所以你就是狗狗按摩師咯
- No. - So you are the dog masseuse?
女士 我就是個陌生人
Ma'am, I'm a stranger.
Buckley 快進來
Buckley, please get in here.
你知道我沒法出門
You know I'm not allowed outside.
好
Okay.
女士 你說你無法出門 是什麼意思
Ma'am, what do you mean, you're not allowed outside?
- 我做了個去皮術  - 那是你的牧師嗎
- I had a face peel. - Is that your reverend?
- 他剝了你皮嗎  - 你說什麼
- Did he peel your face? - I'm sorry?
你需要幫助嗎
Do you need help?
誠實的告訴我 你需要幫助嗎
Answer me honestly. Do you need help?
我需要
I do.
17美元現金一小時 不上稅
It's $17 an hour cash, under the table.
你需要簽一個保密協議和安樂死協議
You'll need to sign an NDA and a DNR.
你坐直升飛機會暈嗎
Do you get sick in helicopters?
從沒有過
I never have.
你得每天早上六點到
You'll need to be here by 6:00 every morning
送Buckley上學
to get Buckley up for school.
然後在十點把我弄起來 但是不許叫醒我
Then get me up at 10:00, but don't wake me up.
我能表達一下我對這個機會
Can I just say how grateful I am
的感激之情嗎
for this opportunity?
不好意思 你叫什麼
I'm sorry. What is your name?
- Kimmy  - Kimmy
- Oh, it's Kimmy. - Kimmy.
你編發技術怎麼樣
Are you good at braiding hair?
- 特別厲害  - 太好了
- I'm awesome at it. - Fantastic.
當然 得先領你去見我的馬們
Of course, you'll have to meet the horses first.
- 要喝水嗎  - 不用了 謝謝
- Do you want a water? - No, thanks.
好的
Okay.
這是Charles 家教
This is Charles. He's a tutor.
他會教你做Buckley的作業
He'll help you do Buckley's homework.
還有 明天就是Buckley的生日
Also, it's Buckley's birthday tomorrow,
所以你得做一個蛋糕 可愛的
so you'll need to make a cake that's cute
但同時要符合石器減肥食譜
but also paleo.
瑞典式按摩 90分鐘 中等力道
Swedish, 90 minutes, medium pressure.
我要睡覺了
I'm going to bed.
我了個去 我找到工作了
What in the ham sandwich? I just got a job.
拜託告訴我你很正常
Please tell me that you're normal.
我需要個能說話的人
I need someone here to talk to.
哦 我特別正常
Oh, I'm very normal.
發生在我身上的都是最正常的事兒
I've had everything normal happen to me.
搞啥
What?
Lillian 我的娃娃傢具怎麼在馬路牙子上
Lillian, why is my doll furniture on the curb?
因為我只能搬的動這些
Because it's all I could carry.
明天真正的搬家公司會來 Titus 把你轟走
Tomorrow real movers come, Titus, and evict you.
- 你怎麼敢  - 你知道我愛你
- How dare you? - You know I love you.
Lillian 我可幫你洗過澡
Lillian, I helped you take a shower once.
- 嗨 大家  - 嘿 白鬼奇葩
- Hey, guys. - Hey, white weirdo.
我找到工作了
I got a job.
17美元一小時 不上稅
It pays $17 an hour, under the tables,
但是我現在就能交房租
but I can pay in advance right now
用我 退的稅
with my... tax refund.
今晚我就能把他東西搬走
I can have his things out by tonight.
Lillian
Lillian.
我決定要室友
I have decided I will be taking a roommate.
哦 你決定了 是嗎
Oh, you have decided, have you?
是啊決定了
Yes, I've decided.
我才是打廣告的人
Well, I'm the one that placed the ad...
其實 我比較想和別人一起住
Actually, I would rather live with someone.
我比較習慣有室友的感覺
I'm kind of used to having roommates.
好啊 同意
Okay. J'approuve.
我什麼時候才能拿到錢
When will I be getting my money?
我的錢呢
What about my money?
- 奴隸制賠償都上哪去了 Lillian  - 算你在理
- Slavery reparations, Lillian. - Touché.
你們的確遭了不少苦
You people have suffered.
那是真的機器人嗎
Is that a real robot?
現在的人都有機器人了
Do people have robots now?
- 啥 - 啊
- What? - Huh?
那是我的房間
That's my bedroom.
你就住我辦公室
You'll be staying in my office.
我會在這住的很舒服的
Ha! I will be very comfortable in here.
簡直有兩個Cyndee乘一個Gretchen大
It's like two Cyndees by a Gretchen.
窗戶 我的私人小窗
A window. My own window!
還有這個
And it has this.
你別的東西呢
Where's the rest of your stuff?
就這些了
Oh, this is it.
- 你有秘密  - 啥
- You got a secret. - What?
你帶著滿滿一包現金來紐約
You moved to New York City today with a bag full of cash,
別的什麼都沒有 除了這頂明顯的假發
no stuff, and what is clearly a wig.
有人藏著事兒啊 快說吧
Somebody in here got beans. Spill them.
好吧
Okay.
真相就是 我是從印第安納來的
Well, the truth is, I'm from Indiana...
原來如此
Oh, okay.
怪不得你那麼接地氣
That explains why you're so basic.
別說了
Say no more.
那我們快點把租房子這檔破事撂清楚吧
So let's get this dirty rent business out of the way.
如你所知 我們已經欠了Lillian兩個月房租了
As you know, we owe Lillian two months' back rent,
那是950塊
so that's $950.
加上這個月的
Plus this upcoming month.
當然 還有一個月的押金
And, of course, there's a one-month security deposit.
還有 自從你搬進來 這燈就不行了
Also, ever since you moved in, this lamp stopped working.
所以又是100塊
So that's another $100.
想得美 Titus
Nice try, Titus.
裡面根本沒燈泡
There's no light bulb in there.
被你發現了 你真世故啊
You got me! You are so very cosmopolitan.
所以你今晚打算幹嘛
So what do you want to do tonight?
說實話嗎 一個人一邊聽戴安娜羅絲的專輯
Honestly, listen to Diana Ross albums alone
一邊做拉伸排排氣
while I do my stretches to alleviate my gas.
我們得出去慶祝慶祝
We should go out to celebrate.
我今天找到工作了
I mean, I got a job today.
我有地方住了 我遇到了你
I got an apartment. I met you.
好羡慕你 我都沒遇到過我自己
I envy you. I've never been able to meet me.
來嘛 我們去個酷炫的地方跳舞
Come on, we should go dancing someplace cool,
就像<Moesha>裡面的孟買俱樂部
like Club Bombay from Moesha.
<Moesha>美國九十年代情景喜劇
呃 印第安納還真夠落伍的
Whoo! Things are behind in Indiana.
我買單
I'll pay for everything.
*我去我去*
*I'm going out I'm going*
嘿你想跟我們一起玩嗎
Hey, do you want to party with us?
想來點"莫莉"嗎
Are you into molly?
某種興奮劑別稱
那可不 她是我最喜歡的"美國女孩"玩偶了
Am I? She's my favorite American Girl doll.
Titus 跳舞現在關鍵的是屁股了
Titus, dancing is about butts now.
沒錯
It is, girl.
真棒
It's really, really good.
這樣跳舞更簡單
Yeah, it's easier to dance.
- 是啊 我去給我們拿點喝的  - 好啊
- Yeah. I'm gonna go get us drinks. - Okay.
嘿 我不想拋下你的
Hello. I do not want to abandon you,
不過我被那個合唱團的帥哥
but I've been invited to have Korean food
約去吃韓料了
with that pretty chorus boy.
去吧 好好玩 哦對了 Titus
Yes, go have fun. Oh, hey, Titus?
這個雙肩包會不會太幼稚
Does this backpack look babyish?
這可是個雙肩包
It is a backpack.
- 嘿  - 你知道嗎
- Hey. - You know what?
你是這兒最辣的女孩
You're the hottest girl in here.
說的跟真的似的 在相反日吧
As if. Opposite day.
酒精 好好喝 我喜歡
Ugh, alcohol... tastes good. I like it.
你的頭髮好香
Your hair smells good.
他們在醫院裡檢查過我有沒有頭蝨
They checked it for lice at the hospital.
- 我有點想吻你  - 好啊
- I kind of want to kiss you. - Yes.
來吧 沒問題
Do it. I'm fine.
臥槽 我的包呢
What the fudge? My backpack.
有人搶了我的背包
Someone yanked my backpack!
別管它了
Don't worry about it.
閉嘴 我的錢在裡面
Shut up. My money's in there.
好了 你出去
All right, let's go.
你得幫我找到它
But you got to help me find it.
是個紫色的JanSport
It's a purple JanSport.
Buckley 這還不算你最糟糕的生日
Actually, Buckley, this isn't your worst birthday ever.
最糟的那次是你猛擊了我的下部
You worst birthday ever was when you busted my genitals.
我很抱歉 我一晚上沒睡 我所有的錢都被偷了
I'm so sorry. I was up all night. All my money got stolen,
自從我的電子雞死了以後一直都沒鐘
and I haven't had a clock since my Tamagotchi died.
這是你的第三振 出局
Uh-uh, this is strike three.
一振二振去哪了
What were strikes one and two?
棒球也改規則了嗎
Has baseball changed?
嘿 香艷一夜啊 我也是 剛剛坐下來
Hey, walk of shame. Me, too. Just sat down.
你沒事的 你沒事的 你是個人
You're okay. You're okay. You are a person.
這是你的家
This is your home now.
你還有扇窗
Look, you have a window.
加把勁 Kimmy
Come on, Kimmy.
行不行 你這個廢物 Kimmy
Come on! You're garbage, Kimmy!
三思啊 姑娘 我還在睡覺呢
Reconsider, girl. I was sleeping.
他們偷了我的背包
They stole my backpack.
- 什麼 - 我做不到
- What? - I can't do this.
- Richard牧師是對的  - 等等 誰
- Reverend Richard was right. - Wait, who?
Richard Wayne Gary Wayne牧師
Reverend Richard Wayne Gary Wayne,
高級先知 以及
senior prophet and CFO of Savior Rick's
- 救世主裡奇的恐怖天啟之幽靈教堂的首席財務官  - 啥
- Spooky Church of the Scary Apocalypse. - Foo?
我是四個印第安納鼴鼠女之一
I am one of the Indiana Mole Women.
新聞裡的 你幹嘛不告訴我
From the news. Why didn't you tell me?
因為我只想做個普通人 可我做不到
Because I just want to be a normal person, and I can't.
我什麼都不知道
I don't know anything.
我連手機和相機都分不清
I can't tell phones from cameras.
連警察都有紋身了
Even policemen have tattoos.
把你的破東西都打包好
Pack up your trifles and whatnots.
- 什麼  - 帶上你的東西卷鋪蓋走人
- What? - Get your things and go home.
紐約不適合你
New York City is not for you.
- 你不懂  - 我太懂了
- You don't understand. - Oh, I do understand.
- 但是 Titus  - 孩子
- But, Titus... - Girl.
我不叫Titus
My name is not Titus.
我的真名是Ronald Wilkerson
My name is Ronald Wilkerson.
1998年我坐著輛該死的巴士
I came here in 1998 on a damn bus
從密西西比州契卡索縣來到這兒
from Chickasaw County, Mississippi.
你知道有誰離開過契卡索嗎
You know who leaves Chickasaw County?
沒人
Nobody.
你有見過從密西西比來的人嗎
Have you ever met a person from Mississippi?
沒有 但我還沒見過什麼人呢
No, but I haven't met anybody.
我的重點是
My point is...
這是那時的我
This was me then.
天真吧 和你一樣
I was cute, just like you.
一笑八顆牙 和你一樣
Showed my teeth when I smiled, just like you.
我把名字改成了Titus Andromedon
I changed my name to Titus Andromedon,
然後去參加了<獅子王>的試音
and I marched myself in to audition for The Lion King.
你在百老匯演<獅子王>
You were in The Lion King on Broadway?
沒錯 除了我沒有
Yes, except I was not.
15年來我去<獅子王>試了20次音
I auditioned for The Lion King 20 times in 15 years
直到他們終於告訴我
until they finally told me,
"你直成這樣是過不了的"
"You are not passing as a straight giraffe."
但你唱的那麼好 我聽到了
But you are such a good singer. I heard you.
我已經三年沒表演過了
I have not sung in public in three years.
想知道我現在在幹嘛嗎
You want to know what I do now?
我穿上那個機器人服去時代廣場
I dress up in that robot costume in Times Square,
幫一個遊樂場發傳單
and I pass out flyers for an arcade.
我老闆才17歲 我工資都是按美分計的
My boss is 17 years old, I get paid in quarters,
而且我最近突然意識到
and I'm starting to think
出租車司機是不是故意撞我的
cab drivers are hitting me on purpose.
可你從密西西比出來了
Well, you got out of Mississippi.
逃跑不等於混出頭了 Kimmy
Escaping is not the same as making it, Kimmy.
我都不太敢問你這個問題
I'm very scared to ask you this...
好吧 我們在地底下的確有過彆扭的性行為
Yes, there was weird sex stuff in the bunker.
讓我說完
Let me finish.
你包裡有多少錢
How much money was in your backpack?
一萬三
$13,000.
*不不不不*
*No, no, no, no*
為什麼
Why?
拿回你的租金 給自己買張車票
Take your rent money back, buy yourself a bus ticket,
然後離開這裡
and leave this place.
但你會被趕出去的
But you will be evicted.
別擔心我
Don't worry about me.
我很美 但我很堅強 就像鑽石
I'm pretty but tough, like a diamond...
或是穿著晚禮服裙的牛肉乾 走吧
or beef jerky in a ball gown. Go.
該死
Ugh! Gosh dang it.
噢 神秘聖誕老人
Oh, Secret Santa.
噢 Cyndee
Oh, Cyndee.
我剛才
I was talking...
在和我的好朋友上帝聊天
to my good friend God earlier.
我們在聊為什麼他要讓自己創造出來的東西
We were talking about why he allowed his creation
被毀滅
to be destroyed,
地下的土壤 天上的禽鳥
the earth of the land and all the fowls of the air
還有海里的海猴子
and the sea monkeys of the sea.
你知道他對我說什麼嗎
And do you know what he hath told me?
我們既蠢又壞
That we're all dumb and bad
所以他就讓世界被毀滅了
and that's why he let the world be destroyed?
一點沒錯 Gretchen
That's exactly right, Sister Gretchen.
Richard牧師
Reverend Richard?
我想不通 整個世界都被毀了
I was wondering, the whole world was destroyed,
所有東西都死了 對不對
and everything died, right?
沒錯 除了你們這些小笨蛋
Except for all you dum-dums here, yes.
那為什麼
Then how come,
我之前清理空氣過濾器的時候
when I was cleaning out the air filter earlier,
發現了這個
I found this!
如果所有動物都死了 這隻老鼠是哪兒來的
If all the animals are dead, where'd this rat come from?
該死 Kimmy Schmidt 我要滅了你
Damn you, Kimmy Schmidt! I will break you!
你滅不了的
No, you won't.
Titus Andromedon
Titus Andromedon!
Ronald Wilkerson 我知道你在裡面
Ronald Wilkerson, I know you're in there.
你來這幹嘛 糊塗女傭
What are you doing here, Amelia Bedelia?
<糊塗女傭>美國兒童繪本人物 各種誤解主人的意思
我都叫你回印第安納了
I told you to go back to Indiana.
我不回去了
I'm not going back.
我不會放棄 你也不準
I'm not gonna give up, and neither are you.
我是想保護你
I'm trying to protect you.
保護什麼
Protect me from what?
我人生中最慘的經歷
The worst thing that ever happened to me
已經在我家前院發生過了
happened in my own front yard.
生活把你打趴下了 Titus
Life beats you up, Titus.
不管你是被邪教帶走了
It doesn't matter if you get tooken by a cult
還是試音被拒了一次又一次都沒關係
or you've been rejected over and over again at auditions.
有些東西是你必須經歷的
Some of which you paid to attend.
你可以縮成一個球然後死去
You can either curl up in a ball and die,
就像我們以為Cyndee死了的那次
like we thought Cyndee did that time,
你也可以站起來說 "我們與眾不同
or you can stand up and say, "We're different.
我們是強者 我們堅不可摧
g ones, and you can't break us."
我們會付租金 我會找回工作
We are going to pay the rent, I'm gonna get my job back,
我還會吻一個男孩
and I'm going to kiss a boy.
你會去格萊美唱歌
And you are going to sing at the Grammys
和惠特尼休斯頓還有邁克爾傑克遜一起
with Whitney Houston and Michael Jackson.
均已去世
例子夠爛 不過沒錯
Bad examples, but yes.
為這些人兒歌唱吧
Just sing for these people!
這才是你在這裡的原因
Because that is what you came here to do.
*這是生命的輪迴*
*It's the circle of life*
*一起唱*
*Singalong-a Hey, la agawaga*
*它感動我們所有人*
*And it moves us all*
*大家一起唱*
*Singalong-a Hey, la macarena*
*這是輪迴*
*It's the circle*
*生命的輪迴*
*The circle of life*
電波字幕組 歡迎您的加入
官方網站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@電波字幕組
*我們堅不可摧*
*Unbreakable*
*簡直是奇跡 她們活下來了 臥槽*
* They alive, damn it * * It's a miracle *
*堅不可摧 她們活下來了 臥槽*
* Unbreakable * * They alive, damn it *
*但是女人可真牛逼啊*
*But females are strong as hell*
*堅不可摧 她們活下來了 臥槽*
*Unbreakable They alive, damn it*
*這是奇跡 堅不可摧*
*It's a miracle Unbreakable*
*她們活下來了 臥槽*
*They alive, damn it*
*女人可真牛逼啊*
*But females are strong as hell*
*我們在這裡住了十年*
*We've been living here ten years*
*沒人見過什么女孩*
*Nobody seen no girl*
*沒人聽見女孩的聲響*
*Nobody heard no girl*
*沒人見過什么女孩*
*Nobody seen no girl*
*他把她們關在地下*
*He had them underground*
*她們破土而出 四處張望*
*They come out their hole Looked around*
*就像一群土撥鼠*
*Like a bunch of Punxsutawney Phils*
*然後我說 Nathan 這是真的嗎*
*And I said "Nathan, is this for reals?"*
*一 二 三 四個女孩出現了*
*One, two Three, four girls come up*
*堅不可摧 她們活下來了 臥槽*
*Unbreakable They alive, damn it*
*這是奇跡 堅不可摧*
*It's a miracle Unbreakable*
*她們活下來了 臥槽*
*They alive, damn it*
*但是女人可真牛逼啊*
*But females are strong as hell*
*堅不可摧 她們還活著 臥槽*
*Unbreakable They alive, damn it*
*這是奇跡 堅不可摧*
*It's a miracle Unbreakable*
*她們活下來了 臥槽*
*They alive, damn it*